

## Skills:

- HTML5
- Css/Scss/Sass
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Angular
- Vue Js
- WordPress
- \* Social Media Marketing
- \* Word Office
- \* Github
- \* Adobe Photoshop
- \* illustrator
- \* Adobe Xd

## **Spoken Langouges:**

English Turkish

\*\*\*

Farsi

\* \* \* \*

53

54

55

56 57 58

## **Contacting Me:**

0410289893

mona.jadidian@gmail.com

## **Mona Jadidian Karimi**

```
2
3
   Courteous and enthusiastic, I am interested in IT and everything in its
  orbit. Since 2019 I began to be fascinated by web programming,
   E.g. developing and designing websites. I am keen to gain more experience in
  the field .For this reason, I am looking for a company willing to
   to offer me a placement among their Developers. In return, I would
  offer my full commitment, and share my knowledge to your team.
   I am therefore currently looking for a job as a junior Front-end developer.
   Click here for my portfolio https://mona1987-jk.github.io/Cv.protfolio.lv/
11
12
13
14
       Education and Degrees:
15
               2008-2012 :Bachelor in ICT Engineering ICT Management
16
              2012-2013: Certificate of ICDL (IT-Basic concept of information
17
              Technology)
18
              2012-2013: Certificate of ICDL (Windows-Using of Computer & Files
19
              Management)
20
              2019-2020: Certificate of JavaScript
21
              https://www.sololearn.com/Certificate/1024-16104699/pdf/
22
              2019-2020: Certificate of CSS
23
              https://www.sololearn.com/Certificate/1023-16104699/pdf/
24
25
26
       Employment History:
27
27
               2019-2021 : junior Website Developer(design and build up
               the responsive webpages as I add some of them on my Cv)
-Intimate knowledge of HTML,CSS, and JavaScript.
-Experience in developing responsive web application.
-Experience developing and testing components and applications in vueJs.
28
29
30
31
32
                - Experience working with group in github.
                -Excellent English language communication skills, both
33
               verbal and written.
34
               -Took a design and convert it into a functional
35
               website/web application.
36
               2016-2018 : English Teacher
37
               2015-2016 : English Grammar and speaking Teacher in Iran
38
               2014-2015 : It Department in Iran(work in supporting department's network and fix issues in Rama Electronic
39
40
               Industry)
41
42
       Projects
43
                            https://mona1987-jk.github.io/coffee-seed/
44
                            https://mona1987-jk.github.io/wild-life/
45
                            https://mona1987-jk.github.io/clothes-shopping-
46
                            online.lv/.
47
                            https://mona1987-jk.github.io/hair-salon.lv
48
49
50
51
52
                              https://app.magnificent-art.com/
```

https://www.magnificent-art.com/